

# Rekunova Maria

#### Info

8 February 1997 Kyiv, Ukraine ma.rekunova@gmail.com +38 (063) 726 60 43

#### **About Me**

I am a highly organized digital designer & developer. With a passion for animation and strong attention to details, I'd like to put my skills, experience, and creativity to use to help bring your projects to life. I am proactive, productive, and ready to work on challenging projects to expand my knowledge, improve my English, and reach new achievements together.

## Languages

**Ukrainian** Native

Russian Native

**Englsih** Upper - intermediate (B2)

German Beginner (A1)

#### **Hobbies**

Sport, painting, travelling, cinematography

#### Education

2014 - 2018 Bachelor Degree

Specialist in automation and computer-integrated technologies

Kyiv National University of Technologies and Design

**2018 - 2019**Master Degree

Computer systems and automation reserch engineer

Kyiv National University of Technologies and Design

## Skills

• HTML5, CSS3/SASS

After Effects/motion design

Javascript (basic)

GSAP animation library

• Photoshop, Figma, Illustrator

• Sony Vegas

• Web design/development

Understanding BEM principles

### **Experience**

July 2019 - present time

# Digital Designer

Inskin Media

- creating mock-ups for a range of devices using providing assets & following brand guidelines;
- developing rich media adverts using HTML, CSS, JS/Query
- usage of GSAP animation library, native CSS3 animation, sprite sheets;
- collaborating with international teams, going through a manager-client process, managing multiple campaigns at any one time

September 2018

Junior Digital Designer

Inskin Media

April 2016 -January 2017 Shop-assistant

Argo

June 2015 -August 2015 Cashier

Novus

## Certificates

First Certificate in English Kyiv, 2014

FCE confirms an upper-intermediate level of English

## Personal Qualities

Responsible, proactive, highly organized, detail-oriented, problem solving, communicative, easy-going